let questions6 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to alert",
      answer: "B. warnen",
      options: [
        "A. ignorieren",
        "B. warnen",
        "C. verschweigen",
        "D. übersehen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "broadcast",
      answer: "C. Sendung",
      options: [
        "A. Aufnahme",
        "B. Anzeige",
        "C. Sendung",
        "D. Zeitschrift"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bulletin",
      answer: "A. Nachrichtenmeldung",
      options: [
        "A. Nachrichtenmeldung",
        "B. Werbespot",
        "C. Dokumentation",
        "D. Interview"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "bump",
      answer: "D. Beule",
      options: [
        "A. Riss",
        "B. Narbe",
        "C. Wunde",
        "D. Beule"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to chop",
      answer: "B. hacken",
      options: [
        "A. schneiden",
        "B. hacken",
        "C. reiben",
        "D. schälen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "closet",
      answer: "C. Schrank",
      options: [
        "A. Regal",
        "B. Kommode",
        "C. Schrank",
        "D. Truhe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to console",
      answer: "A. trösten",
      options: [
        "A. trösten",
        "B. ärgern",
        "C. ermahnen",
        "D. warnen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "district",
      answer: "D. Bezirk",
      options: [
        "A. Stadt",
        "B. Region",
        "C. Land",
        "D. Bezirk"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "drawer",
      answer: "B. Schublade",
      options: [
        "A. Fach",
        "B. Schublade",
        "C. Kiste",
        "D. Regal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to endure",
      answer: "C. ertragen",
      options: [
        "A. vermeiden",
        "B. ignorieren",
        "C. ertragen",
        "D. fliehen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to execute",
      answer: "A. hinrichten",
      options: [
        "A. hinrichten",
        "B. verhaften",
        "C. verurteilen",
        "D. bestrafen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to grasp",
      answer: "D. festhalten",
      options: [
        "A. loslassen",
        "B. werfen",
        "C. berühren",
        "D. festhalten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "rear",
      answer: "B. Rückseite",
      options: [
        "A. Vorderseite",
        "B. Rückseite",
        "C. Oberseite",
        "D. Unterseite"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "senator",
      answer: "C. Senator",
      options: [
        "A. Richter",
        "B. Minister",
        "C. Senator",
        "D. Diplomat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "skull",
      answer: "A. Schädel",
      options: [
        "A. Schädel",
        "B. Knochen",
        "C. Wirbel",
        "D. Rippe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to stir",
      answer: "D. umrühren",
      options: [
        "A. schütteln",
        "B. mischen",
        "C. kneten",
        "D. umrühren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to tap",
      answer: "B. antippen",
      options: [
        "A. schlagen",
        "B. antippen",
        "C. drücken",
        "D. stoßen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "tremendous",
      answer: "C. gewaltig",
      options: [
        "A. klein",
        "B. normal",
        "C. gewaltig",
        "D. mittel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "underneath",
      answer: "A. unterhalb",
      options: [
        "A. unterhalb",
        "B. oberhalb",
        "C. neben",
        "D. zwischen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "worm",
      answer: "D. Wurm",
      options: [
        "A. Schlange",
        "B. Raupe",
        "C. Käfer",
        "D. Wurm"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export default questions6;